<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>

    <!-- Plastic Facts -->
    <string name="abPlastic_pFactSubHead"> The Facts </string>
    <string name="abPlastic_pFactsIntro"> \ - Plastic bottles are made from the easiest type of plastic to recycle.
        \n \n
        - Plastic bottles make up 53% of all household plastic waste.
        \n \n
        - 38.5 million plastic bottles are used every year.
        \n \n
        - 23.5 million plastic bottles are recycled every year.
        \n \n
        - 15 million plastic bottles are NOT recycled every year.
        \n \n
        - 700 thousand plastic bottles are littered every year.
        \n \n
        - Plastic bottles can take up to 450 years to decompose in landfill.
        \n \n
        - 73% of all fish contain some form of plastic.

    </string>

    <!-- Types of Plastic -->
    <string name="abPlastic_TypesSubHead"> Types Of Plastic </string>
    <string name="abPlastic_TypesMainText"> There are 7 different types of plastic, the first is the
        easiest to recycle and the last is the hardest. Bellow are all the different types </string>
    <string name="abPlastic_pet"> Used for fizzy drinks, water bottles and salad trays.
        PET is widely recycled back into the manufacturing of items such as textiles, clothing,
        food and beverage containers. </string>
    <string name="abPlastic_hdpe"> Used for milk bottles, bleach, detergents and some shampoo
        bottles. It is easily recyclable back into items such as non food containers, detergent
        bottles and floor tiles.</string>
    <string name="abPlastic_pvc"> Used in the manufacturing of carpet backing, pipes, window and
        door frames and fittings within the home. Where recycled, it is used for the
        remanufacturing of packaging, paneling, guttering, electrical equipment, traffic cones
        etc </string>
    <string name="abPlastic_ldpe"> Used commonly for bin liners, packaging film, squeezable bottles
        and carrier bags. After being recycled it’s use is common in the manufacturing of shipping
        envelopes, bin liners and carrier bags.</string>
    <string name="abPlastic_pp"> Used in the packaging of food and non food containers, margarine
        tubs, microwaveable meal trays. It’s fibres are also used for carpets, wall coverings and
        some vehicle upholstery. It’s use after recycling the material is very similar to it’s
        originally designed purpose.</string>
    <string name="abPlastic_ps"> Used for packaging protection uses especially electronic goods and
        toys whilst in transit, some foods such as hamburger boxes, egg cartons, and yoghurts. PS
        is not typically recycled, but please check with your local recycling facility.</string>
    <string name="abPlastic_other"> Other plastics that do not fall into the categories above may
        be highlighted with the number 7 logo or the word other.</string>



</resources>